AVC Sub-Thai translated by Basilano
Published at AVCollectors.com only
"Stepmother swings charm"
this
That my father had told me that she was looking for a new mother
Hello
Happy to know
From today
Calling her Mae La
Say goodbye
From now on, my mother will take care of herself.
New mother?
How is your stepmother?
Heard that her stepmother was both beautiful and young
Really jealous
Actually
Why are you not happy too?
What's going on?
Is your stepmother scolded?
A scary person
what?
You don't want to tell anyone.
Back?
I'm back
Today the school is fast.
Went to take a shower and came to eat cookies
When I saw what I was doing with my father, right?
Mee?
What?
See, right?
Didn't see anything
C. Just hear the sound ~~
Feeling uncomfortable, so woke up a bit
What did Khun Aun do with my father?
Why did you fix the fabric and stuck with your father like that?
It's not a big deal.
dress
You are already growing up.
Should know what men and women have to do with the fabric
Soma does not have to be shy.
Have you ever seen a girl fix the fabric?
I've seen girls changing their costumes at the gymnasium ~
and
When the children used to see the mother to fix the fabric as well
Like that
Want to know why adults have to fix the fabric?
Eh?
Will tell you
Eh, really?
Come here
See your mother clearly?
Clear ...
See what?
Eh? It's ~?
What is it
Inside wet too
Why wet
When women are excited ...
Inside, Jim ....
There will be delicious water coming out.
Water ...... Delicious water?
Yes
Enough to know, right?
I'll see more.
Eh? What else?
Ah ... Ah ... It can move too.
Mother, it bounces too.
Yes? Is there anything else?
Eh
Want to see more than this?
Wouldn't it be good?
Yes
What is this mother?
Haha, that's what I said.
Try tapping.
Ah, there?
Yeah!
Both shirts in underwear
Normally, dress like this?
Want to see more?
... ... ...?
This inside is very interesting ..
Want to see?
Well
Here
So big
Do this then, right?
Yes
Top
This mountain will have a peak.
Mountain peaks?
do you want to try?
Want to see more?
If you want to see
This is the water that says delicious, right?
Yes
Oh, Mae Ha, this is it
There are caves in the mountains.
Hahahahahahahahaha, never seen
If you grow up, you will see more.
really?
With water coming out from the cave as well
There is a stream inside.
Streams?
, It will flow out here
What is your mother here?
How did he peak?
Peak? Is this the peak?
Yes
Want to try tapping?
Eh? Can you tap?
Don't know?
Don't know
How to tap?
Is this the peak?
Let's try to touch it? --Hmmm
Good
Why is it stronger?
It ~ ah ~,.
dress
Ah ...
What?
- already dropped Being eaten?
It ate inches? ——
Sucked in and then ~ sucked in ~ ~
Why does the cave eat my fingers?
If you put your finger in that way
- Will be eaten?
Keep doing that
Very good
Doing this will not be eaten?
Why do I feel that my finger is still being eaten?
Ah ... that way, well.
Ahhhhhh, your finger is good ..
Well?
- Yeah ~~~
There are white things too. What is it?
Is good ~~
I think I don't see anything inside.
Continue on
Don't take your finger away.
Good ~~
Ah! Will be finished ~
Will be finished ahh ~
What is it?
What will it be? ~
What?
Top
Come out ~~
See?
The water flows out ~~
Come out a lot
See if you're moving? ~~
Don't tell her father.
Do you understand?
Don't take this cave to tell anyone.
Can't sleep?
But thinking about the daytime, right?
What do you do?
Gently ~
Is a good boy
Mom will help
How is the lips? Otherwise, it will be bitten.
Want to see breast milk?
Try to catch it.
How are you
Like?
How is this?
I'll use your hand for a while.
Like water will come out again
Are you going to the cave? ~
Lightly ~
How are you using your hands?
Excited?
Is a good boy
What do you do?
Quietly
Excited ~
Mom is licking his head.
Quietly
Father is sleeping ~
Want to sleep as well
Want to continue?
Well
Mum
Will leave
Really good
Like it?
I'm back
Please help me
I brought my friends to play at home.
Come in
Both beautiful and young
Hello, kids ~
Why don't you eat?
What will you play today?
Drink water ~
-Thank you
You are so beautiful.
Eh ~ No, yeah.
Mom, I don't see beautiful like you.
Really beautiful
Will you go out and play outside?
Today is very good.
We want to play games.
What games?
Want to play hide secretly
So can play in the house
Yeah ~ Bravo ~~~
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 Good secret?
Well, then? ——
Will start
Where are you? Is this right?
I found out
The rest
Already found
How do you know that you are here
Feet appearing
Cheers ~~ It's fun.
- Find out too soon.
So let's help find water?
Eh? Looking for aunt?
So hide it.
1 2 。。。 How to start?
Where are you?
Haha already found
Found then stupid ~~
- How can I find it?
Are you here?
found it
so bad
My eyes
Will you find it?
1 2 3 。。。 I will find it.
Let's eat sweets first.
What do you do? Where to go to hide?
Come to avoid this first
10, where to hide?
Is this way?
How do
Hide this
Act like a puppet
Still can't find Sohu and Khun Aun at all
So try this way better ~~
To hide above
This mother is great.
I can't find it because of this. ——Hmm.
beware
This place is really narrow.
Would like to open the cave to see again
Exciting ~
Mee?
The story that we did last night ~
Why should I see the mother cave forever?
Then ~ adult, he likes to play
Then?
Adult play?
Kiss a little? Eh? Kiss?
-Yeah
That way
First kiss? ——
Doing this will be good? If I knew it would be okay?
Large ——
Want to catch anything?
This is milk ~
Big breast milk ~~
Very big ~
Soft with ~
Can I see the cave?
Want to see your mother's butt?
Bounce well?
Top to this.
Shallow dance?
Will soon wake up
Can't suffocate?
-Yeah
Will be removed
Put on white pants, really cute.
Look yummy
The hair is not up yet.
Do you want me to do it like last night?
Yeah!
Ah, delicious.
delicious
How is it?
Catch milk
Breast milk is so soft.
See the tits? ~~
Want to suck breast milk?
Get up ~
Is it delicious?
- delicious
Here is a little care.
Excited?
Hungry?, Looking for something to eat?
Ah ... here? It's,
- Want to see the cave, right?
Yeah ~ suck a little
How is the taste?
Ah ~ very tasty
Delicious?
-Yeah
Want to see inside the cave?
What?
Lie down
Can you put it into the mother's cave?
Can you?
Really?
Put into the cave
Tight?
Go in
- Entered
Feeling strange. What's this?
Inside the cave
Mom will move slowly.
Oh ~
is it good?
Blush
Do you like it?
Like it ~
It goes in and out too.
- Yes.
Like being in heaven ~
First time, right?
Mom is excited too ~~~
Ah ~~ · ~~
Do it faster?
Yeah ~~
Top
Can you hear the sound of water from the cave?
Mother is the best ~~~
Top
Full of water ~
Mom will break the neck ~~
Mae Ha, the best.
Look at
Yeah, strange.
It's eating sausage, right?
Yes
Think of this cave?
Inside it ~~~
They are finding us.
Are coming
They must meet us.
They were found
They can't find me. Don't worry.
Have you gone?
I think I didn't hear anything.
Good
Know what? They came out of this cave ~
Really?
-Yes
When doing this There will be children born.
Kids?
Yes
Feel good ~
The water will flow out of the cave ~
Come ~~
Never mind ~~~
So good ~
Will be finished
Feel the cave that is squeezing?
Ah ~
Put it back into the cave
To put it in?
Yeah!
Here
Find the cave
Is this?
Ah ~~ It's not.
Right here?
- Yes. Ah ~~ Ah ~~~
Go in, right?
Go in
Ah! Go in
Can handle the cave
Siao-chan ~~~
Good ~~~
Like a dog
Come here
Where to go?
So much ~
Of course, it will die ~~~
Continue, put it in.
Yes? Continue?
Blush ~
Will be put in?
Like that
Ah, inside it is warm.
Don't make noise like that ~
Mom didn't want to make a little noise.
Did I do something bad?
No, it's very good.
Better than her father
really?
Not the same She made it very warm.
Like it so much
Want to catch breast milk?
Like this
Like this?
Yes
Very soft
Come close
Mother ~~~
Siao?
Hah ~~
Like this position?
Yeah!
Be a good boy!
Do you know ~
Made for a long time Still fit ~
Want to be released yet?
Released a lot
Can you kiss your mother?
so good
Is there anything?
Feel strange
Feeling strange? Is it nearing completion?
Eh?
It's almost finished.
Close to
What? ~
Let go inside
Are you out?
What is this?
As you know Which caused the children to come up?
Children?
Yeah!
Don't know anything
It's really a little kid.
Want to try another round?
Huh? Again?
Ahh, this is really super sensitive.
I think the sound is loud.
Like having something out again?
delicious
Take out a lot
Already close?
Really?
Can be released into the mouth
Eh? really? It will be dirty.
- Never mind.
Let's shoot.
Go ahead?
Shoot at all
Ahh! ~~~~~~
Ah, then ~~~~~
Full shot
It's super delicious ~
Lots of water
Another round?
Eh !!
The next day
This just can't be done.
Make it look
Super
Around again
Really good
Be careful
Hard to lose
Must be like this
Like a beggar
- Dirty Chib
Like zombies
Yes
Look at your face
Jokingly patched?
Really
Why is this so dead?
Enjoy playing a little bit.
Not strong, and it doesn't matter again.
Wait, let's drink first.
Water?
Can
Can drink
Shower too
- Tinned
This rope jump is good.
Here they are.
Mee?
They are so dirty.
Wait, they will be told by their mother.
Wait a minute to wash.
But .. we are embarrassed ~
Mee?
Are they shy?
Why be shy?
Don't know ...
It's embarrassing.
Take it hard
The pants were messy.
what
Take off quickly
but...
What is hidden inside?
There may be soil attached here.
Must be cleaned
Here you
Know then?
Want to do the same?
They are extremely dirty. The water must punish you.
Mee? Don't take it?
What are you doing?
Who made them so dirty?
What?
Like this
Why is it so hard?
What are you thinking about?
Do you like the skirt?
Isn't it exciting?
Are you still excited?
Want to see the butt?
Oh! Would like
Top
How is it like this?
Very soft
Soft ~
They are here
Is a really bad boy
Are you excited?
Ho! Nice
Excited?
Oh ~ !! The top is so beautiful.
Hit the nipples too
Do you like each other?
All sausages
I'll clean it for a while.
Really cute little sausage
Use saliva to help.
This sausage is completely messy.
I'll clean up the sausages for you.
How do you know?
Shy ~~~
Lick here and then
right?
Really good
Sweet sausage
Ah ~~ Delicious
Fight for yourself.
Have you ever seen anything like this?
Have you ever been
Never watch porn movies?
Like this, it's not funny.
Tell the water
Like I saw yesterday
Saw a little
Can you tell me?
- Tinned
Aunt will not continue if they refuse to tell.
Ever secretly watched the girls in the bathroom ~
Hahahaha, so I'll continue.
It's not a big deal.
Shy?
Doing this, right?
Will make it faster
Little sausage
Rub it on the bottom
They look tired.
I will shoot.
Ah ~~~ Shoot it.
Sausage has water coming out too.
I'm sorry
Come here
Remove the pants to be smooth.
But left the shirt
dress!?
Open wide legs ~
Shy?
Siao?
Yes
How are you?
Like being finished
Come to finish
Well?
will be done
Done ~
Oops ~~~
Ah ~~~
Look
Top ~~
Delicious food
They are very good.
Do you like each other?
Thank you for letting me try some delicious stuff.
Mother, don't do this.
Father is just here.
Can be caught
If quiet, there is no way to know.
Can't do this
Don't forget to drink milk.
Want to drink milk from the breast?
Good drink
There are still plenty of milk.
This is just a free gift.
Is it delicious?
Say soon that the mother's milk is delicious.
Take it .. Drink a lot ~
Still a lot
delicious
Milk comes from a lot of breasts.
Big breast
Hurry, drink it all.
Value ~
Walk fast
Running
You don't really matter.
I am so bad
Doesn't really matter
Please help
Try two people.
Two horses
Be careful
- Running fast
~ Fun ~
Worst
Say yes, be careful.
Will make it look as an example
Eh!? Your mother will look like an example?
Look
what's wrong?
What to do?
I'm not going to ride on top. Let's look here.
What are you watching?
Does anyone want to try riding?
I am
How is it?
-Hi
Shook his tail as well
How are you
Mom, isn't it hard?
Damn Haha ~
Running
Big run
Top
Who's that? Can't see it at all?
Yes, Aunty?
Do they ride like this?
Think yes
Let's play for another round.
Want to play? Do you have children?
Yes? Adult play?
How are you?
Play like this, fun?
Please give me some kisses.
Ah, so bad.
Please me
With pleasure
what's wrong? what's wrong
Full nose
Ah
Good to wear?？
Want to try licking?
Can you play like this
Want to play
Ah ~~ Top
I like this
Take the sausage to the mother to play
Is it okay?
Like it will be stronger
Is it hard?
So what to do? ~~~~~
How is this?
Why is it stronger?
Lol, really cute
Mae Ha, mother, the room is hot?
Yes, very hot
So take off
Eh?
Remove
Nice
How is breastfeeding?
I caught it.
Catch it
Never mind, right?
Okay
How to play? Good?
Can you play together?
Can
Mom will deal with the sausage.
- Catch this kind of fun.
Yes.
This is super soft.
Don't see like my mother
Unlike her mother?
Like?
- Yes
Siao Chan
Can play as you like
I ... I want to play again.
Want to ride again?
Want to ride
The sausage is bigger.
Khun Aun
- What?
I like milk
So?
Want to suck
So come and suck together
Great.
- Continue to suck.
so good
Like this
Please also
- Want to be the same?
Do you want too?
What is this?
- Try sucking.
Beautiful women are good.
Like that
- Do you do this? / Yeah
Lick like this?
Yes
Good lick
It's completely wet.
Come here, kids, take it out to see it.
Take off?
Yeah ~~
Shy, friend?
Take it off. Don't be shy.
Take it all out to everyone
Excited?
Excited
Ah ~
- All of the sausages have been removed.
Mom, I'll lick all three sausages together.
Lick?
Yes
How to lick the blessing? All three are good?
Want to lick all?
Come in all
Ask me first
Haha, not all at once.
Mother looks
Can do
Nice to meet everyone
Top
This sausage is really delicious.
Adults, do they play like this?
Yes
dress!?
Must be kept secret?
Secret?
Can you?
Ah ~ good ~
What is it?
I can't stand it.
Want to come and explore the cave?
-Well
You guys look good ~
This posture
Right here, right?
like this
-Yeah
Mom once told me
Put the sausage in here
you see
- Cool Cheddar
See each other?
Blush
Good
I want to see this big milk.
Siao Chan
Ah well
Oh, the top
This is the best, right?
Ah ~~~~~~ Growing really fast
Oh ~ super cool
This time when the women are super sensitive It will be nasty.
Do you understand?
Good
The two of you are not violent with my mother.
Yes
Let's play together
That is the best.
The sausage feels good.
Come this way
Want to do from behind?
Want to do backwards?
Thinking behind?
Khun Aun is awesome.
To be the outstanding mother of the year
Here?
- Mom will give
Enter yet?
- Entered
Super
Best of all
Try moving yourself.
How are you?
Excited?
Best of all ~
How do you feel?
Super excited
Good
Once put in, I can't see it.
Want to do with him?
Would like
Do you know today, my mother is exceptionally good mood?
Oh, Khun Aun moved himself too.
I can feel inside.
How are you
Well, right?
Strange but like
Lie down
Will make you try
Put inside the cave
Top
Come very heavy
How are you?
I want to hug it.
- come to hug
Ah ~~ Top
Everyone is really good.
Is the water moving well?
Please see clearly.
See?
Blush
Top
Well, right?
~
Change your position
Great, right?
Most of all
They come here
Let's play together
Sausage I like very much.
Good
Take turns playing.
May I continue?
Mom came here.
What to do?
Let's ask first
Put it in full.
Need to put it in?
-
Put it in full.
Need to put it in?
-
Put it all out.
Continue to do so.
I think I'm close to being finished.
Is it finished?
- Tinned
almost there
Into the cave ~~
Can you let the water out?
I couldn't see the cave so I had to let the water go.
Today, every sausage must be in the cave.
Really?
Come and move together
-Yeah
arrived
Siao Chan
Will leave
Let go inside
Already released?
It's fun.
Come out a lot
Super sensitive
Top
Feel good, right?
Yes
May I put some sausages in?
Will do it faster
Shy
Mom moved.
Ah mum
The two of you come to see.
Super
Sausage with water flowing out as well
Do it soon.
All out
Fully
Full release
All out, right?
Mix together two people.
Anyone left?
Sausage will enter the cave ~
Lying down below
Go in
Listen to the sound
Nipples already set
Siao?
Like?
All out
Want everyone to come in
They will have more children.
Eh? brother?
- Yes, you will have a sister.
And then have more friends to play
Come soon
Ahh
Shoot at all
Ah, then shot
Very good
Too much
So full
Feel good?
Hi
The old water is sad.
The sausage is getting bigger.
- Really? Look at it.
It's good.
So let's continue.
Be good like this, if you want to be released again.
Do this well.
Really?
So continue to do so.
I will fight again
- Again
Do that
I will release the water again. ~
So warm
Oh, still a lot like the same.
Somu ~~~
Will wear it
Like this, right?
- Tinned
This is the best.
really?
- Tinned
But would it be good?
Put a lot of water into the mother's cave like this.
It doesn't matter.
Somu and Father, also have the same blood line
We have children together.
Really?
It's okay?
- Yes
She's so cute.
Mother, I will let the water go.
- good
I released it again.
Would look messy all over
Have fun today?
This cave is always ready. If you want to release
-Yes!!!
Is a good boy
Tried very well
- Tinned!
Oh! Like being frozen again
Will you die?
Why is it so angry?
Stay playing together like this all the time.
Can you play all the time?
If they are good kids
- Lae !!!
Translated by Basilano